# Xun Li

0444557114 | xunli253@gmail.com | Hobart https://xunli253.github.io/ | www.linkedin.com/in/xunli-308715206 | https://github.com/xunli253

# **PERSONAL SUMMARY**

Information Technology graduate with 2+ years of experience. I am looking to join a team with whom communication and teamwork are paramount. Having much experience working with JavaScript/TypeScript, I would jump at any opportunity to continue growing my skillset in the field of Full-Stack development.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AMC Agency Aug 2021 - Mar 2022

Web developer internship, IT Department

Hobart

- Implementing web application with React, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JSON and responsive Web Design, and RESTful API.
- Based on Mongo DB, design database table.
- Designing and coding application components in an Agile environment utilising a test driven development approach
- Splitting the web page into independent components, and design reusable components.
- Using functional component and react Hook to implement reusable component.
- Collaborating with the development team to analyse and understand business or user requirements to create detailed database design models.

#### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

CourtCanva Sep 2022 - present

Developer

 The Project is develop a web application for court design. Customers can choose different template or customise their court, and administer can conduct information interaction and management.

- Use Jira to manage task progress and Git as version control tool and Whole project follow the Agile development principle.
- Implemented web application with React, TypeScript, Next.js and Responsive Web design.
- Use Nest.js, MongoDB, Mongoose to provide RESTful API.
- Use React Konva to draw courts.
- Use Redux to manage the application state and applying middleware such as reduxthunk.
- use Axios calls and requesting JSON information through REST APIs to fetch data and secure client's information from serve asynchronously.
- Split the web page into independent components, and design reusable components.
- Design and write a readable, maintainable, reusable global components style, unified naming conventions, and avoid global variable pollution.
- Use Functional component and react Hook to implement reusable components.
- Preforms Unit Test with Jest.
- Stand up meeting every evening and sprint refinement meeting on Sunday of every new sprint.

# **Raffle Drawing Application**

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

#### Team member

- Developed a raffle drawing iOS application with Xcode for organiser of a raffle. Users
  can use the APP to create, edit, and delete multiple raffles and draw a winner.
- Implemented functions in Swift including selling tickets, drawing a winning ticket, editing raffle seating and customer details, uploading images and sharing ticket information to other application.
- Increased usability by deleting redundant buttons and input filed and adding autocompletion feature.
- implemented 10 rounds usability tests to ensure the App can run smoothly even if users make errors

#### **Research Assessment Program**

Jul 2019 - Nov 2019

#### Team member

 Developed research assessment program for administrative staff to monitor and assess the research performance of staff and research students using publicly available information about their employment and publication outputs.

- Implement functions include filtering publication list by year range, filtering research list by level or partial name match, and assessing staff performance in C#. Saving 35% space by creating specific class.
- Implemented LINQ to SQL to connect with the SQL server database and implemented LINQ to Object for retrieving, manipulating and querying data.
- Developed the rich visual components through WPF using XAML.
- Used Binding, Styles, Data Template, Control Template, Routed Events, Converters, Layout Panels in XAML.

## Bank Website | School Project

Feb 2019 - Jun 2019

Team member

- Built a bank website for Secure Bank Pty. Ltd, including functions such as Accounts,
   Transactions, eStatements, Transfer & pay, Manage, and Message to increase, to increase their business and attract more customers.
- Designed 8 responsive and consistent pages using HTML, CSS, jQuery, PHP to create.
- implemented MySQL database to record 100+ pieces of users, administrator, bank transaction information.
- Use JSON and Ajax for data communication.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Tasmania**

Feb 2019 - Dec 2020

Master of Information Technology

Hobart

High Distinction/Distinction achieved in Software Application Design and Implement, ICT System Strategy and Management, Enterprise Architecture and Systems, E-Logistics, Network Security Techniques and Technology, and Multi-perspective ICT Project.

JR Academy Mar 2022 - Jul 2022

Full Stack Development

# **SKILLS**

#### Front-End:

HTML5, CSS, Sass, JavaScript/ES6, Typescript, React.js, Next.js, Redux, Redux-thunk, Responsive Design, JQuery, npm/yarn

## Back-End:

Node.js, Nest.js, express.js, C#, JWT Token, PHP, Java, Swift

## Database:

MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySql, SQLite

# **Develops Tools:**

Visual studio code, intelliJ IDEA, pgAdmine, GitHup, Postman

## Teamwork:

Agile, Scrum, Gather, Jira

## API:

Ajax, RESTful API, JSON, PostMan, Google Maps Embed API